locu.com 2019-02-05

# Privacy Policy | Get Found

At Locu, Inc. (“we” or “us” or “our”), safeguarding your privacy as a user of www.locu.com and/or any other websites, widgets, APIs and services we provide (collectively the “Service”) whether as a paying member or just as a visitor (collectively, “User(s)”) is important to us. Accordingly, we have created this privacy policy (the “Policy”) to explain how we collect, use, disclose and protect your personal information as it relates to your use of the Service.

## EU-U.S. & Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield

Our parent company, Go Daddy Operating Company, LLC (and our related entities, including GoDaddy.com, LLC, Wild West Domains, LLC, Blue Razor Domains, LLC, Starfield Technologies, LLC, Domains by Proxy, LLC, Outright, Inc., Media Temple, Inc. and Mad Mimi, Inc.) participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Privacy Shield Framework. We are committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on each Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield Frameworks, and to view our certifications, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s [Privacy Shield List.](https://www.privacyshield.gov/)

Locu, Inc. is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Locu, Inc. complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Locu, Inc. is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Locu, Inc. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.>

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

## Information We Collect

### Information You Provide to Us:

We collect any information that you submit to us voluntarily through the Service or provide to us in any other way. For example if you register for the Service you must provide us certain information, such as your name, email address, phone number, and create a password. If you are a business registering for the Service, we may also request additional information, such as your physical address, photos, logos, hours of operation, accepted forms of payment, fax number, and in connection with your payment for the Service, information pertaining to your credit or debit card and billing address.

### Information Collected From Others:

We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, and combine this data with information we already have about you.  This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you.  If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

Examples of the types of personal information that may be obtained from public sources or purchased from third parties and combined with information we already have about you, may include:

  * Address information about you from third party sources, such as the U.S. Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud, and
  * Purchased public data about our customers from third party databases that is combined with information we already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products.

### Information Collected Automatically:

We may also receive or collect certain technical information when you use our Service, such as the internet protocol (“IP”) address of your computer, the IP address of your internet service provider, mobile device ID, the date and time you access our Service, the IP address or URL of the website from which you linked directly to our website, the operating system you are using, the Internet browser you are using, the sections of the website you visit, the website pages read, images viewed, and third party links, advertisements, and offers from our partners that you click-on or other content that you may access or download from the Service.

### Email:

When you e-mail us, we are collecting the information you include in your e-mail communication to us.

### Cookies and Web Beacons:

Locu.com and its partners use "cookies and other similar tracking technologies” to deliver and to enhance the use of the Service. A “cookie” is a small amount of data that gets installed on the hard drive of a User's computer serving as an anonymous unique identifier and allowing the website to recognize future visits using that User’s computer. We use tracking cookies to analyze User behavior on our site. For example, the information provided through cookies is used to recognize you as a previous User, to offer personalized web page content and information for your use, and to otherwise facilitate your experience in connection with our Service. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. However, you may choose to decline cookies if your browser permits, but please be aware that doing so may affect your use of the Service (such as logging in to your account) and your ability to access certain features of our Service.

We may use “web beacons” to compile tracking information related to our email campaigns. A “web beacon” is an electronic image, also called a "gif," that may be used on website pages to deliver cookies, count visits and compile statistics on usage and campaign effectiveness or in our e-mails to tell us if an e-mail has been opened and acted upon. None of the tracking information in these reports can be connected to the identities of individual Users.

## How We Use Your Information

Pursuant to the terms of this Policy, we may use your personal information for the following purposes: 

  1. Provide access to the Service and verify your eligibility for the Service;
  2. Provide customer support to assist you with your questions and/or concerns;
  3. Billing and payment for the Service;
  4. Administer your account with us and customize the Service to suit your needs (i.e., by tracking and analyzing your preferences);
  5. Advise you of changes to our Service, or new services that we may implement from time to time;
  6. Send you promotional communications through e-mails and notices on our website, which preferences you may control by contacting us or logging in to the Service; and
  7. For other purposes as outlined in this Policy.

## Sharing Your Information

The information we collect is used to improve the content and the quality of our Service, and without your consent we will not otherwise sell, license or share your personal information to/with any other party(s) for commercial purposes, except: (a) to provide the Service, (b) when we have your permission, (c) or under the following instances:

### Locu Partners:

We may use the information you provide us about your business, such as address, phone numbers, hours of operations, and menu content to supplement or improve the content we make available through our Service, including our website, widgets, and/or API. We may also share that information with our partners so that the information can be updated on such partner sites and for other marketing and related purposes. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at [info@locu.com](mailto:info@locu.com).

### Service Providers:

We may use third-party service providers (e.g., for our web hosting, network, hardware, software, storage, and/or payment processing needs) to manage one of more aspects of our business operations, including the processing or handling of personal information. When we do use an outside company, we use contractual or other appropriate means to ensure that personal information is used in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. By registering for the Service and providing your credit or debit card details to us, you permit us to use your provided credit or debit card information to bill you for the Service subscription you purchase. Additionally, by providing your credit card details to us, you consent to and authorize us to provide your credit card details to payment processors and financial institutions necessary to process your payment for the Service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

### Legal Disclosure and Business Transfers:

We may disclose your personal information as permitted or required by law without your consent, if we are compelled to release information by a court of law or other person or entity with jurisdiction to compel production of such information (e.g., subpoenas). Additionally, if we have reasonable grounds to believe information could be useful in the investigation or prevention of improper or unlawful activity (i.e., suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service), we may disclose information voluntarily to law enforcement agencies or other appropriate investigative bodies without obtaining your consent before doing so.

Locu may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personal information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. If Locu is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## Links to Third-Party Websites

Our Service contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by "clicking on" a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

## Securing Your Personal Info

Locu endeavors to safeguard personal information to ensure that such information is kept private. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [info@locu.com](mailto:info@locu.com).

We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. However, unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, the inherent insecurity of the Internet and other factors, may compromise the security of your personal information at any time. Therefore we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information.

## International Users

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the Service is hosted in the United States. Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in the United States. As a result, United States federal and state governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through laws applicable in the United States. Your use of this Service or your submission of any personal information to us will constitute your consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of your home country, including the United States, which may provide for different data protection rules than in your country.

## Children and Minors

The Service is not intended for use by minors under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly solicit any information from or market to such minors. If you are a parent or legal guardian who discovers that your child has provided us with information without your consent, you may contact us at [info@locu.com](mailto:info@locu.com). We will delete such information from our files.

## Changes

We may periodically update this Policy at our sole discretion. We will post any changes to this Policy to our website, and if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, in some cases, email notification of such changes). Please ensure that your primary e-mail address on file with us is correct.

## Access

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us at [info@locu.com](mailto:info@locu.com).

You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by contacting us at [info@locu.com](mailto:info@locu.com). We will respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe.

## Choice

### Advertising

We also partner with a third party to display advertising on our websites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) [or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)]. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

## "Do Not Track" Signals

Note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to websites and online services you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you may wish to visit ([www.allaboutdnt.com](https://allaboutdnt.com/)).

## Opting Out

We may send you communications regarding our Service, including (without limitation): (a) notices about your use of our Service (including any notices regarding violations of such use), (b) updates to our Service, and (c) promotional information and materials related to our Service. You may opt-out of receiving these promotional e-mails and other promotional communications from us at any time by e-mailing [info@locu.com](mailto:info@locu.com) with your specific request. We will respond within a reasonable timeframe. Please note, however, that opt-out requests will not apply to non-promotional system messages (e.g., transactional service messages, security alerts, update notices).

## Contacting Us

Any questions, comments or concerns about this Policy should be addressed by e-mail to [info@locu.com](mailto:info@locu.com) or to:

Locu.com

14455 N Hayden Road

Scottsdale, Arizona 85260

480-505-8877
